[Music]
i got this sweater from a lovely
neighbor of mine
she told me it was a vintage piece that
she thought i may like to use when
making videos
she was right it's beautiful but also so
warm that i barely need to wear anything
under it if i'm exercising outside on a
sunny day
and i'm grateful because the weather is
finally warmed up a bit and i can get
out and move and break a sweat simply by
wading through the snow
[Music]
i have never seen this much snow in my
valley
it nearly reaches my hip in certain
places
and with that comes some concerns there
was an avalanche up the road from me so
we're being a little more careful than
usual when iger and i take our walks and
choosing safe routes
the bobcats and cougars are more active
as well
seeking lower ground and very hungry so
we need to be cautious about that
[Music]
while i am careful i'm never fearful
living out here
because i've always seen my relationship
with the wildlife as my responsibility
to preserve
i'm the intruder here
not the bobcats and coyotes
i need to reverently walk these roads to
show respect when i see them
not get too close and turn away if they
are large predators or i sense my
presence makes them uncomfortable
it is my small way to try to preserve
some sense of harmony and
offer my gratitude for everything they
do
[Music]
after a long day of playing in the snow
the next morning i was in the mood to
stay indoors and keep warm
and what better thing to do on a cozy
day but some baking
today i'm taking inspiration from a very
old cookbook that has been in my family
for as long as i can remember
as you know i predominantly share
desserts on this channel because i am a
connoisseur of all things sweet and
while unfortunately i cannot eat cake
and pudding for every meal lest i suffer
consequences i love to end each and
every day with the dessert of some kind
and today i wanted to make some of my
favorite traditional hispanic dishes
adding my own spin of course as there is
no exact way to make these foods
that's one thing i love of peasant
dishes that use basic ingredients
because experimentation is not only
allowed but expected depending on what
you have on hand
so i altered these recipes slightly to
suit my specific tastes
today i'm making buling de pang iflan
con leche fresca they are two of my very
favorite desserts very popular in puerto
rico
[Music]
it always brings back memories to make
recipes associated with my childhood and
the people in my family that hold
positions of great respect
my abuela media morales experienced a
very difficult start to life
possibly some of the worst you could
imagine
she was born into a dysfunctional
household that went back generations
there seemed to be no end to the cycle
of neglect and yet my abuela decided
enough was enough
she realized it would be easy to become
like those who came before her
letting pain and anger and hurt define
her life
but she didn't want to give others that
power she wanted to be free
so she decided to build something new
it made things no doubt harder for her
and what came was a lifetime of
back-breaking work and struggling to get
out of poverty
but she did it and thanks to her and my
abuelo papa my mommy went to new york
learned english and joined the reserve
she and my papi are veterans and i
cannot imagine being more proud of them
and all they have sacrificed
thanks to these strong men and women not
only do i exist but i don't spend one
day not being aware of how grateful i am
for this
this life
the clean water the food the safety
things could have been so different
i will forever cherish the people in my
life that decided to stop hurting and
start healing
they are heroes because of that and
showed me firsthand
that that is what matters in life
[Music]
i did decide recently that i wanted to
reopen my etsy shop it is something that
brings me a lot of joy and really
inspires me to keep creating art and so
i did decide to reopen it and i
appreciate all of you who have reached
out wondering if i will reopen it i it
has been very motivating and encouraging
i've always been passionate about
words and poetry and i wanted to find a
way to mesh that with my art so i have a
few new things available but i would
love to
get your feedback please let me know
what you think it is kind of a new idea
that has sprung on me as i've been
working on my book project which
thankfully the first draft i think
is complete hopefully i will continue
making progress on that and keep things
updated i am very exciting
i'm very excited
i'm very excited it's been a wonderful
experience so far i wanted to announce
that i'm just very very grateful for
all of you who have sent such kind
messages and support it has
really really helped me out and it has
made so much possible not only these
videos
but also just being able to create more
arts it's also been very helpful as
luke and i have come to this point where
we realized we
want to be able to find a house and
there is absolutely no way that we could
afford afford
a house in this area i think all over
the u.s but just it feels like here as
well it's just housing prices have just
gone crazy and
we have been presented with the
opportunity to get a house that we could
actually afford and that opportunity
will not come again and
we've realized that
you know if we do ever want to be
homeowners in this area we do need to be
able to take advantage of this
opportunity to renovate a barn that
belongs to his parents and make it a
home and so
that's just been a really exciting
prospect and
yeah i'm just
really happy we can find a place so
yeah
i think you know
for me personally i've always wanted my
own home you know just any home it
doesn't have to be the perfect home it
just needs to be a home
and so this opportunity has just been
just so amazing anyway
yeah
i have to admit i'm quite nervous about
a lot of changes coming my way but i
also think that i have found in my
personal experience that i am my best
self and most happy when i kind of
embrace
change and i embrace those fears a
little bit and understand that you know
it's just part of
growing and maturing and and being a
better person so
yeah anyway thank you so much for all
your kind words and messages i hope you
are having a wonderful day or night i
hope you're taking care of yourself i am
sending a lot of hugs and love and i
will see you very very soon
goodbye
you